mizzenandmain.com 2019-05-28

# Privacy Policy - Mizzen+Main

_Updated May 24, 2018_

## Collection of Information

We collect information you provide directly to us. For example, we collect information when you use our websites, shop in our pop ups, create an online account, sign up to receive our emails, participate in a sweepstakes, contest, promotion or survey, communicate with us via third party social media sites, request customer support or otherwise communicate with us.

The types of information we may collect include your name, email address, zip code, billing address, shipping address, phone number, product preferences, demographic information and any other information you choose to provide.

If you make a purchase through our Sites, our third-party payment processor service providers may also collect billing information, such as your first and last name, email address, phone number, credit card or debit card number, and billing and shipping addresses. If you make a purchase over the phone, we will collect this personal information and share it with our third-party payment processor service providers.

### Information We Automatically Collect:

We automatically collect certain information about you when you access or use our websites or transact business with us, including: the type of browser you use, access times, pages viewed, your IP address and the referring link through which you accessed our websites, transactional information of returns and exchanges.

We may use cookies, web beacons (also known as "tracking pixels") and other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you interact with our websites or emails, including information about your browsing and purchasing behavior. We may combine this information with other information we collect about you and use it for various purposes, such as improving our websites and your online experience, understanding which areas and features of our sites are popular, counting visits, understanding campaign effectiveness, tailoring our communications with you, determining whether an email has been opened and links within the email have been clicked and for other internal business purposes. For more information

### Information We Receive From Other Sources:

We receive personal information about you from other sources to help us correct or supplement our records, improve the quality or personalization of our service to you, prevent or detect fraud, and for other business purposes.

### How do you get my consent?

When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.

If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.

If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at info@mizzenandmain.com.

## Cookies Policy

We may use cookies, web beacons (also known as "tracking pixels") and other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you interact with our websites or emails, including information about your browsing and purchasing behavior. We may combine this information with other information we collect about you and use it for various purposes, such as improving our websites and your online experience, understanding which areas and features of our sites are popular, counting visits, understanding campaign effectiveness, tailoring our communications with you, determining whether an email has been opened and links within the email have been clicked and for other internal business purposes.

Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually set your browser to remove or reject cookies, For more information about disabling flash cookies, see <http://www.adobe.com/products/flashplayer/security>. Please note that if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect the availability and functionality of our websites. In addition, many web browsers support Do Not Track technology. If you enable Do Not Track, Mizzen+Main will not use information about your web viewing activities to tailor your online experience. To learn more about third-party tracking, cookies and how to "opt-out" of this type of advertising please go to [www.aboutads.info/choices/](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/). Mizzen+Main intends to follow the Digital Advertising Alliance’s Self-Regulatory Principles except where the law requires us to do otherwise

### Your Choices and Access to Information

Depending on your location and where applicable law requires, you may have the following choices with respect to your Personal Information:

  * The right to access your Personal Information;
  * The right to update your Personal Information by emailing us or, where appropriate, amending the personal details contained in your registered account with us. If practically possible, we will make corrections (where appropriate) based on your updated information;
  * The right to withdraw your consent with respect to Personal Information that is collected on the basis of your consent;
  * The right to request deletion of your Personal Information or object to its processing; and
  * The right to lodge a complaint with us or, as applicable, with a supervisory authority.

If you want to learn more about the Personal Information that Mizzen+Main has about you, or you would like to exercise your choices regarding your Personal Information, including updating or changing that information, please contact us by email at info@mizzenandmain.com.

If you no longer want to receive marketing communications from Mizzen+Main, please follow the “unsubscribe” instructions that are included at the bottom of each message. Please note that if you unsubscribe from our marketing communications, you will still receive order confirmation messages.

### Children’s Privacy

The Services are not directed to children under the age of 16, and Mizzen+Main does not knowingly collect Personal Information or other Information from anyone under the age of 16.

## Disclosure

We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.

## Hosting

Our store is hosted with an ecommerce company. They provide us with the online e-commerce platform that allows us to sell our products and services to you.

Your data is stored through their data storage, databases and the general application. They store your data on a secure server behind a firewall.

## Payment

Our payment system is encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted.

All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover.

PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our store and its service providers.

### Third-Party Services

In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.

However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.

For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.

In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.

As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.

Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.

When you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.

### Google Analytics

Our store uses Google Analytics to help us learn about who visits our site and what pages are being looked at.

## Security

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.

If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption. Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.

### Age of Consent

By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.

If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.

## Questions?

If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact us at info@mizzenandmain.com
